rugby365.com 2007-12-22

# Rugby News, Results, Fixtures and Features from Rugby365.com

**1.** TEAMtalk Media Group Network Privacy Policy:   
ukbetting plc incorporating Sporting Life UK Limited, TEAMtalk Media Group   
Limited, Rivals Digital Media and sites within the company's TEAMtalk Media   
Group Network strongly believe in protecting the confidentiality and   
security of information we collect about individuals. The material below   
describes our privacy policy and describes how we treat the information we   
receive about you if you interact with any of our sites.. 

**2.** We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our website. Your IP address may be used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. We will not provide or sell user-specific demographic information to any other person or business. We will only share this information on an aggregate basis. 

**3.** Our site uses cookies (user data collectors). We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes. It is possible for you to disable these cookies by changing your browser settings, but this may slow down or prohibit access to parts of the site. 

**4.** Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and e-mail address) and demographic information (like their postcode). We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the selected user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt out of receiving future mailings. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data for other purposes, such as tailoring the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This information is shared with advertisers, but ONLY on an aggregate basis. We will NEVER share your address and personal data with any advertiser unless you specifically opt in to one of our/their programs (a sweepstakes, for example). The choice to specifically identify yourself to an advertiser will always be yours. We may occasionally e-mail you items of interest from some of our advertisers. You will have the opportunity to opt-out of such programs, and once again, your e-mail name and personal information are never shared with those advertisers unless you choose to identify yourself to them by participating in offers that interest you. 

**5.** This site contains links to other sites.   
**Rugby365** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

**6.** We use an outside advertising company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our website, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

**7.** This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personal information. 

**8.** This site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

**9.** This site also gives all of its users the ability to read and to post in public forums. The site does not have a filter in place to exclude children from these activities without prior parental consent. 

**Rugby365** uses its best efforts to make the content of its website acceptable for children's viewing. Safeguarding the personal information of children is extremely important to us. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in any interactive activities offered on the site. 

**Thank you for reading our legal section and thank you for choosing

Rugby365 as your reliable source of sports news and views on the Internet. If you have any questions about anything contained in this site, or about your dealings with this site, you can contact Customer Service at   
365 Digital Publishing, Fedsure on Main, Newlands, Cape Town, South Africa or e-mail us on   
[webmaster@365digital.co.za](mailto:webmaster@365digital.co.za).

**
